<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
	DEFAULT PREDICATES
	Predicates.xml
-->
<METADATA
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://gist.githubusercontent.com/milko/f2dcea3c3a94f69bb0bb/raw/715d8fd15a66ad25466c9efc4f767fd31fc9a21a/Dictionary.xsd">
	
	<!-- Default predicates -->
	
	<META>
		<!-- kPREDICATE_SUBCLASS_OF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="SUBCLASS-OF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Subclass of</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the <i>subject of the relationship</i> is a <i>subclass of the object of the relationship</i>, in other words, the <i>subject is derived from the object</i>.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_SUBRANK_OF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="SUBRANK-OF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Sub-rank of</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the <i>subject of the relationship</i> belongs to the <i>next lowest rank</i> than the object of the relationship.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_SUBSET_OF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="SUBSET-OF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Subset of</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the <i>subject of the relationship</i> represents a <i>subset of the object of the relationship</i>, in other words, the <i>subject is contained by the object</i>.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_PART_OF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="PART-OF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Part of</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the subject of the relationship represents a part or component of the object of the relationship, in other words, the subject is part of or is a component of the object.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_TYPE_OF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="TYPE-OF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Type of</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the subject of the relationship represents the type of the object of the relationship. This predicate can also be as a group and a proxy: it may define a formal group by collecting all elements that relate to it, and it acts as a proxy, because this relationship type implies that all the elements related to the group will relate directly to the object of the current relationship.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_FUNCTION_OF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="FUNCTION-OF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Function of</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the subject of the relationship represents a function or trait group of the object of the relationship, in other words, the subject is a group of functions that can be applied to the object.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_COLLECTION_OF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="COLLECTION-OF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Collection of</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the subject of the relationship is a <i>collection belonging to the object of the relationship. This predicate is similar to the <i>attribute of</i> predicate, except that the latter case the subject is a scalar item of the object, while, in this case, the subject is a template for the collection of elements that belong to the object.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_ATTRIBUTE_OF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="ATTRIBUTE-OF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Attribute of</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the <em>subject</em> of the relationship is an <em>attribute of the object</em> of the relationship, this means that the subject of the relationship belongs to the set of attributes of the object of the relationship.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_PROPERTY_OF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="PROPERTY-OF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Property of</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the <i>subject of the relationship is a property of the object of the relationship</i>, this means that the subject of the relationship is a <i>feature</i>.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_TRAIT_OF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="TRAIT-OF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Trait of</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate relates a <i>trait</i> to its category vertex, it indicates that the subject of the relationship is a <i>trait of the relationship object</i>. This predicate is used to connect <i>feature vertices</i> to their parent vertex.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_METHOD_OF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="METHOD-OF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Method of</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate relates <i>method vertices</i> with <i>feature vertices</i> or <i>other methods</i>, it indicates that the subject of the relationship is a <i>method, or workflow variation</i> of the object of the relationship. This predicate is used to connect the <i>pipeline of modifiers</i> applied to a <i>feature vertex</i>.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_SCALE_OF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="SCALE-OF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Scale of</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate is used by <i>scale vertices</i> to <i>connect feature or trait vertices</i>, the subject of the relationship represents a <i>scale or unit</i> and the predicate indicates that the object of the relationship uses that scale or unit. This predicate is specifically used to indicate the different scales in which a feature or trait vertex can be expressed in.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_ENUM_OF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="ENUM-OF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Enumeration of</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate relates <i>vertex elements</i> of an <i>enumerated set</i>, it indicates that the subject of the relationship is an <i>enumerated set item instance</i>. If the object of the relationship is also an enumerated set item instance, this means that the subject is a subset of the object.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_INSTANCE_OF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="INSTANCE-OF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Instance of</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate <i>relates a type to its instance</i>, it indicates that the <i>object of the relationship is an instance of the subject</i> of the relationship.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_AGGREGATE -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="AGGREGATE">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Aggregate</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the subject of the relationship should be <i>aggregated</i> into the object of the relationship, in other words, the subject should be copied into the object. This predicate will be used in general to <i>copy</i> a value from a descriptor belonging to a set specific to a kind of domain into a descriptor which is common to a series of different unit kinds. This is useful for searching among heterogeneous kinds of objects.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_PREFERRED -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="PREFERRED">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Preferred choice</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the object of the relationship is the <i>preferred choice</i>, in other words, if possible, one should use the object of the relationship in place of the subject. This predicate will be used in general by <i>obsolete or deprecated items</i>. The scope of this predicate is similar to the <tt>VALID</tt> predicate, except that in this case the <i>use</i> of the subject of the relationship is <i>only deprecated</i>, while in the <tt>VALID</tt> predicate it is not valid.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_VALID -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="VALID">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Valid choice</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the object of the relationship is the <i>valid choice</i>, in other words, the <i>subject of the relationship is obsolete or not valid</i>, and one should use the object of the relationship in its place. This predicate will be used in general to store the obsolete or deprecated versions. The scope of this predicate is similar to the <i>PREFERRED</i> predicate, except that in this case the use of the <i>subject of the relationship is invalid</i>, while in the <tt>PREFERRED</tt> predicate it is only deprecated.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_LEGACY -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="LEGACY">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Legacy version</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the object of the relationship is the <i>former or legacy</i> choice, in other words, the object of the relationship is <i>obsolete</i> or <i>not in use</i>. This predicate will be used in general to <i>record historical information</i>. The scope of this predicate is similar to the <tt>PREFERRED</tt> and <tt>VALID</tt> predicates, except that in this case the legacy choice <i>might not be invalid nor deprecated</i>: it only means that the object of the relationship <i>was used in the past</i> and the subject of the relationship is currently used in its place.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_XREF -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="XREF">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Cross reference</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the subject of the relationship is <i>related</i> to the object of the relationship. This predicate does not represent any specific type of relationship, other than what the edge object attributes may indicate. The scope of this predicate is similar to the <tt>XREF-EXACT</tt> predicate, except that the latter indicates that the object of the relationship can be used in place of the subject, while in this predicate this is not necessarily true.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
		
		<!-- kPREDICATE_XREF_EXACT -->
		<TERM ns=":predicate" lid="XREF-EXACT">
			<item const="kTAG_LABEL">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT">Exact cross reference</item>
				</item>
			</item>
			<item const="kTAG_DEFINITION">
				<item>
					<item const="kTAG_LANGUAGE">en</item>
					<item const="kTAG_TEXT"><![CDATA[This predicate indicates that the object of the relationship <i>can be used in place of</i> the subject of the relationship. If the predicate is found in both directions, one could say that the two <i>vertices are identical</i>, except for their formal representation. The scope of this predicate is similar to the <tt>XREF</tt> predicate, except that the latter only indicates that both vertices are related, this predicate indicates that they are <i>interchangeable</i>.]]></item>
				</item>
			</item>
		</TERM>
	</META>
</METADATA>
